Washington and Lee University and Regional Virginia History Research Collection WLU.Coll.0668
Washington and Lee University, University Library Special Collections and Archives
- Biography, 1700-2018 (Box 2, Box 2-10)
  - Daniels, Jonathan M., 2006-03-26 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Civil rights; Daniels, Jonathan M., 1939-1965; R. E. Lee Memorial Episcopal Church (Lexington, Va.)
  - Davidson, Charles A. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Davidson, Charles A. (Charles Andrew)
  - Davis, Adelaide Sutro Weinberg, 1995-04-15 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    File includes an article titled "Turning 90 is Just Another Milestone in Lexington Woman's Interesting Life."
    Davis, Adelaide Sutro Weinberg
  - Davis, Paxton, 1994-06-01; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 3, Folder 31)
    Davis, James Paxton, Jr.
  - DeLaney, Ted, 1993-1998; The Roanoke Times; Richmond Times-Dispatch; Winchester Star (Box 3, Folder 32)
    File includes three articles concerning Professor DeLaney's professional career.
    Delaney, Theodore C., Jr., Dr.; Washington and Lee University
  - Denny, George H. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Denny, George Hutcheson
  - Dickinson, Sally Bruce, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    File includes photocopies of newspaper obituaries of her death on December 10,1940. Photocopy of a newspaper article, "U.D.C. Holds Exercises at Sayler Creek Battlefield" at which Ms. Dickinson was a speaker. Photocopy of a page concerning Miss Dickinson's book, "Confederate Leaders."
    Virginia -- Saylers Creek; Dickinson, Sally Bruce; United Daughters of the Confederacy
  - Diehl, George West, 1975; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 3, Folder 35)
    File includes article titled "Service Held for Dr. G.W. Diehl."
    Diehl, George West
  - Dodson, Ryland, 2000-09 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Articled titled "Judge Ryland Dodson Remembers Early 20th Century Tobacco Farming," September 2000.
    Dodson, Ryland
  - Drake, G. Francis, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    File contains e-mail message distributed by the Broadcast Mailer at Washington and Lee on the death of Francis Drake.
    Drake, George Francis
  - Driver, Robert (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Driver, Robert J.
  - DuPont, Jessie Ball (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Du Pont, Jessie Ball
  - Durkin, Kelsey (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Durkin, Kelsey Helen, 1992 - 2013
  - Edmondson, James K. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Edmondson, James K., Colonel
  - Ellis, Powhatan (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Ellis, Powhatan
  - Erwin, Benjamin, 1776-1783 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    File includes biography.
    Erwin, Benjamin, 1755-1822
  - Evans, Lettie Pate Whitehead (Box 4, Folder 4)
    File includes a biography from the Lettie Pate Evans Foundation website and some genealogy from the LDS website.
    Evans, Lettie Pate Whitehead; Lettie Pate Evans Foundation
  - Ewell, Benjamin Stoddert (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Ewell, Benjamin Stoddert
  - Fallon, Gary, 1995; File includes photocopies of two articles concerning the death of football coach Gary Fallon. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Ring-Tum Phi; Fallon, Gary Robert; Washington and Lee University. Department of Athletics. Football
  - Farrar, James Dubois, 1993; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 4, Folder 7)
    File includes two copies of the memorial service program for Farrar's passing and a photocopy of a News-Gazette article titled "Tiger."
    Farrar, James DuBois
  - Feddeman, Fred (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Feddeman, Frederick Augustus
  - Fishwick, Marshall, 2006; The Roanoke Times (Box 4, Folder 9)
    File includes an article titled "He Disciplined Popular Culture" as well as an obituary.
    Fishwick, Marshall William
  - Fithian, Philip (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Fithian, Philip
  - Fletcher, Forest (Box 4, Folder 11)
    File includes a photocopy of the "Washington and Lee Ambulance Unit" from the 1926 Alumni Directory. This photocopy features an article about Fletcher.
    Fletcher, Forest
  - Fletcher, John (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Fletcher, John
  - Fletcher, Laura Mason (Box 4, Folder 13)
    File includes notes on "Miss Laura."
    Fletcher, Laura Mason
  - Ford, Joe H., Jr., 1934; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Rockbridge County News (Box 4, Folder 14)
    File includes photocopies of two obituaries concerning Mr. Ford.
    Ford, Joseph Henry, Jr.
  - Gaines, Edwin Metcalf (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Gaines, Edwin Metcalf, Dr.
  - Gaines, Francis Pendleton, 1930; The Roanoke Times (Box 4, Folder 16)
    File includes a photocopy of Roanoke Times newspaper clipping titled "New President of Washington and Lee."
    Gaines, Francis Pendleton
  - Garber, Sandy, 1880; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    File includes obituary.
    Garber, Sandy
  - Garland, Landon C. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Garland, Landon C.
  - Garrett, William Allan (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Garrett, William Allan
  - Gatewood, James (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Folder includes biography on Mr. Gatewood.
    Gatewood, James
  - Gibbs, James E.A. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Gibbs, James Edward Allen, 1829 - 1902
  - Gorman, Michael K. (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Gorman, Michael K.
  - Graham, Samuel Mercer, 1939-11-30 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    File includes a photocopy of obituary for Mercer Graham.
    Graham, Samuel Mercer
  - Greenberg, Mel, 1974-1998; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); The Roanoke Times (Box 4, Folder 24)
    File includes photocopies of articles concerning the life and career of Mel Greenberg.
    Greenberg, Mel
  - Greenwood, John (Box 4, Folder 25)
    File includes biography on Mr. Greenwood, dentist of George Washington.
    Greenwood, John
  - Groot, Roger, 2005; The Roanoke Times (Box 4, Folder 26)
    File includes a memorial program as well as an obituary by the Roanoke Times.
    Groot, Robert Douglas
  - Hahn, Hilary (Box 4, Folder 27)
    Hahn, Hilary
  - Hall, Carolyn (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Hall, Carolyn
  - Hall, Randolph, 2001-08-25; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 4, Folder 29)
    File includes article titled "Randolph Hall Refused to Fail."
    Hall, Randolph
  - Hamer, Edward, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    File includes memorial program.
    Hamer, Edward B., Jr. (Edward Buck)
  - Hamilton Family (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Hamilton Family
  - Harris, Joyce, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    File includes two photocopies of the Washington and Lee Alumni Magazine with an article focused on Ms. Harris, titled "Still Crazy After All These Years."
    Harris, Joyce
  - Harwood, Doug, 1993-09-19; The Roanoke Times (Box 4, Folder 33)
    File includes photocopy of article titled "Off the beaten path: the Chronicler of Lexington is an institution himself."
    Harwood, Doug
  - Heale, Daniel P., 1864-01-23 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    File includes photocopy of a petition to Jefferson Davis representing that Heale is a citizen of Giles County, Virginia.
    Virginia -- Giles County; Heale, Daniel P.; Davis, Jefferson
  - Higgins, Patty (Box 4, Folder 35)
    Higgins, Patty
  - Hite, Malinda (Box 4, Folder 36)
    File includes an appendix titled "The Mystery Woman."
    Hite, Malinda
  - Hobson, J.P., 1988; 1869 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    File includes a photocopy of a biographical sketch of Hobson by Charles Lee Hobson, March 5, 1998. Photocopies of two papers by Hobson entitled "How I came to Elizabethtown, Kentucky" and "How General Lee Came to Washington College." Photocopies of a letter to Lee concerning Hobson (1869) and a Louisville Times article about the letter.
    Hobson, John Peyton; Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward)
  - Holland, John Gill (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Holland, J. Gill
  - Hotinger, Harvey Lewis (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Hotinger, Harvey Lewis
  - Hotinger, Myrtle (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Hotinger, Myrtle
  - Howe, James Lewis, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    File includes a photocopy of essay titled "James Lewis Howe - Chemist and Philatelist."
    Howe, James Lewis, Jr.
  - Howerton, James Robert, 1924-1932; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Article includes biography and obituary concerning Howerton and his wife Mary N.
    Howerton, James Robert; Howerton, Mary N.
  - Huber, Helmot (Box 4, Folder 43)
    Huber, Helmot
  - Hudson, Frederick (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Hudson, Frederick
  - Hull, Margaret Jones, 1996-10-09 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    File includes notes on Mrs. Hull, a source for Eleanor Roosevelt's Visit to Goshen Recalled."
    Virginia -- Goshen; Hull, Margaret Jones; Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Hutcherson, James Morrison (Box 4, Folder 46)
    File includes 27 photocopies of letters, transcripts, notes, etc. on Mr. Hutcherson, Washington and Lee University Class of 1902.
    Hutcherson, James Morrison
  - Ipsen, Ernest, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    File includes a letter concerning Ipsen's chauffer, as well as photocopy of portrait of Lee painted by Ipsen.
    Ipsen, Ernest
  - Jackson, Stonewall, 1991; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Frederick Ladies Relief Society (Box 5, Folder 1)
    File includes "Stonewall," a commemorative section of The News-Gazette concerning the Jackson Statue Rededication. In addition, a set of remarks and notes by Mayor Derrick and papers of lectures given by Mary Coulling, Robert F. Hunter, James I. Robertson, Jr., and the Frederick Ladies Relief Society. Program and brochure.
    Jackson, Thomas Jonathan (Stonewall)
  - Jackson, Stonewall, The Roanoke Times; Rockbridge County News (Box 5, Folder 2)
    File includes article titled "Window on the Past: An Unusual Tribute to Stonewall Jackson;" "'Stonewall' Jackson's Grave;" "Jackson Day," and many more copies of similarly focused articles from local newspapers. Also included a brochure reprinted and distributed by Stonewall Jackson Memorial Incorporate, Lexington, Virginia, "The Religious Character of Stonewall Jackson," an address by James Power Smith, D.D., Captain and A.D.C. Staff of General Jackson. The address was delivered at the Inauguration of the Stonewall Jackson Memorial Building, Virginia Military Institute, June 23, 1897. A printed map showing all of Stonewall Jackson's movements, Compliments of Stonewall Jackson Memorial, Inc., Lexington, Virginia.
  - Jackson, Stonewall (George Moor) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    File includes eleven photocopies, black and white and color of Moor as Jackson, one of which is at Virginia Military Institute. Two color photos.
    Jackson, Thomas Jonathan (Stonewall); Moor, George
  - Jefferson, Thomas, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    File includes article from The American Art Journal titled "Gilbert Stuart's Portraits of Thomas jefferson" as well as a photocopy of the Spring 1982 article, "The Adams-Jefferson portrait Exchange."
    Jefferson, Thomas
  - Jenks, James Alley (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Jenks, James Alley
  - Johnson Family (Box 5, Folder 6)
    File includes photocopies of obituaries and photographs concerning the Johnson and McDowell families.
    McDowell family; Johnson Family
  - Johnson, Porter (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Johnson, Porter
  - Johnson, W.T., Rev., 1899 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    File includes a photocopy of inside cover of "Closing Exercises of Privat School."
    Johnson, W.T., Rev.
  - Johnston, William Preston (Box 5, Folder 9)
    File includes photocopy of biography from "Dictionary of American Biography."
    Johnston, William Preston
  - Jones, John, 1882-1883; 1 Item (Box 5, Folder 10)
    photocopy
    Biking Through Albemarle with John Jones, Scottsville Museum, Capturing Our Heritage
    Jones, John; Albemarle County, Virginia
  - Jordan, Harry (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Jordan, Harry
  - Jordan, John, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    File includes a copy of a magazine titled "The Iron Worker" as well as handwritten and typewritten copies of "A Sketch of Colonel John Jordan (1777-1854)
    Jordan, John
  - Joynes, Edward Southey, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    File includes a booklet titled "Edward Southey Joynes: Father of the University and Life Trustee of Winthrop."
    Joynes, Edward S.; Winthrop University
  - Ju, I-Hsiung, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    File includes a magazine article titled "A Chinese Master Opens Western Eyes to Eastern Art."
    Ju, I-Hsiung
  - Junkin, George, 1968-1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    File includes various pieces, including "The Unusual of Lieutenant George C. Junkin, C.S.A.," a discourse commemorative of George Junkin delivered in the West Spruce St. Presbyterian Church, and "George Junkin and His Eschatological Vision," and "Secession Fever on a Southern Campus."
    Junkin, George, 1798 - 1868
  - Junkin, William F. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Junkin, William F.
  - Kahle, Matthew, 1939-1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    File includes articles titled "Matthew Kahle's Log" and "Old George, 1844."
    Kahle, Matthew
  - Kamen, Stan (Box 5, Folder 18)
    The file includes a brochure for The Stan Kamen Collection of Western Art at Washington and Lee University.
    Kamen, Stan
  - Kateley, Jack, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    File includes a biography, obituary, funeral and memorial services programs.
    Kateley, Jack
  - Kempton, Melvin, 1928-1955 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    File includes an obituary (dated August 1, 1955) and two Athletic Association certificates for cross country, 1928 and track, 1929.
    Kempton, Melvin
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - King, Martin Luther, First Baptist Church (Lexington, Va.); Lee Chapel (Washington and Lee University); Watts, Laura; Styles, Spottswood (Box 5, Folder 22)
    File includes various copies of programs of "A Celebration of the Life of King," bulletins for churches, as well as various programs, which includes Black History Month.
    The 2010 Black History Month program includes the following: Poem, "From the Shanty to the White House," by Laura Watts; "Ground Hog Poem," by Spotswood Alexander Styles; "What If There Were No Black Folk?," by Barbara Leahy, 1998.
    King, Martin Luther, Jr.
  - Kozak, Samuel Joseph, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    File includes a memorial service program held at Lee Chapel on July 5, 1997.
    Kozak, Samuel Joseph
  - Labro, Philippe, 1988; Washington Post Company (Box 6, Folder 1)
    File includes a photocopy of a newspaper article concerning Labro, November 12, 1988.
    Labro, Philippe
  - Lacy, Beverley, Rev. Dr., 1900; Rockbridge County News (Box 6, Folder 2)
    File includes an obituary from the Rockbridge County News, November 8, 1900.
    Lacy, Beverly Tucker
  - Lafferty, John James, 2016-01; 1 Item (Box 6, Folder 3)
    J. J. Lafferty: A Remarkable Life, Secrets of the Blue Ridge
    Lafferty, John J.
  - Latane, William (Box 6, Folder 4)
    File includes information concerning the burial of Latane and a painting of and poem about the burial.
    Latane, William
  - Latture, Rupert N., 1974-1995; Richmond Times-Dispatch; The Roanoke Times; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    File Plan
    File includes a photocopy of a Richmond Times Dispatch newspaper article, "Retired Prof. Latture: Living Landmark at W&L," March 4, 1974; a commemorative stamp envelope signed by Washington and Lee University Presidents, Denny through Wilson; and obituaries by The Roanoke Times and the News-Gazette.
    Latture, Rupert Nelson
  - Lauck, C. Harold, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    File includes an article titled "America's Baskerville Printer."
    Lauck, Charles Harold
  - Lauck, Charley, 1999-10-13; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    File includes article from the News Gazette titled "It's a Lauck!"
    Lauck, Charley
  - Lee, Annie, The Roanoke Times; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Peniston, Robert C. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    File includes an article concerning the death of Annie Lee by The Roanoke News; a copy of music sung at Ms. Lee's funeral and the Washington and Lee memorial service; articles titled "Famous Daughter Laid to Rest at W&L" and "Annie Lee's Remains Now in Lee Chapel"; a program, In Memoriam Anne Carter Lee; invitation to private memorial service and luncheon at Lee House; remarks made by Mary Coulling at the private memorial service; remarks made by Capt. Peniston at the private memorial service for Annie Carter Lee; two color postcards of her grave and monument at Warren County, North Carolina; and an excerpt from a letter written at West Point, concerning the young gentlemen.
    North Carolina -- Warren County; Lee, Annie Carter; United States Military Academy; Lee Chapel (Washington and Lee University)
  - Lee, Elijah, 1910; Rockbridge County News (Box 6, Folder 9)
    File includes an obituary of Mr. Lee, former Mayor of Buena Vista.
    Virginia -- Buena Vista; Lee, Elijah
  - Lee, George Bolling, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    File includes article concerning the death and burial of Dr. G.B. Lee by the Ring-tum Phi.
    Ring-Tum Phi; Lee, George Bolling
  - Lee, George Washington Custis, 1913-1996; Iversen, Eve; Watts, Jeri Hanel; McCabe, W. Gordon; United States. National Archives and Records Administration (Box 6, Folder 11)
    File includes obituary of Lee by the Ring-tum Phi; "From West Point to Fort Point: The Story of George Elliot and Custis Lee"; "Major-General George Washington Custis Lee"; "Last Battles: The Wartime and Postwar Careers of Custis Lee"; and photocopies of items at the National Archives concerning G.W.C. Lee.
    Ring-Tum Phi; Lee, George Washington Custis
  - Lee, Henderson, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    File includes a booklet with an article titled "Reverend Henderson Lee: Father of Presbyterianism in Lunenburg County."
    Lee, Henderson, Rev.
  - Lee, Henrietta E., 1864 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    File includes an article titled "The Manly and Upright will Brand Your Name Infamy."
    Lee, Henrietta E.
  - Lee, Mary Randolph Custis, 1865-1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    File includes article titled "They Surrendered Honorably," an excerpt from a letter to her cousin Caroline from Derwent, and a collection of letters from Mrs. Mary Custis Lee to the Snowden Family of Alexandria, Virginia entitled "My Dear Louisa."
    Lee, Mary Randolph Custis; Snowden Family
  - Lee, Mildred, 1905-1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    File includes copies of letters containing information suggesting that G. Campbell Brown, stepson of Gen. Richard Ewell, began courting Mildred Lee and later proposed to her. In addition, the file includes an article concerning the death of Mildred Lee's death.
    Lee, Mildred Childe; Brown, Campbell (George Campbell Brown), 1840 - 1893
  - Lee, Robert E., Gaines, Francis Pendleton; Scott, George C., 1927-1999; Chester, Samuel H.; Elrod, John W.; McCrummen, Norman H., III; The Free-Lance Star; Lee, Agnes; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Staunton Spectator (Box 6, Folder 16)
    This file includes twenty-seven separate items. Of these items, there are various brochures and booklets entitled, "Robert E. Lee: Innovative Educator," "Notes on a Visit to Robert E. Lee," "Lee: The Final Achievement," and "Robert E. Lee and Stonewall Jackson Returned to Lexington, Virginia."
    In addition, the following articles: "Furtherance of Southern Education was Lee's Goal;" "Aging Successfully: The Example of Robert E. Lee;" "How Gen. Lee Came to Washington College;" "After 32 Years, Lee-Jackson Painting on Display;" "General Lee After the War," from the magazine The Century Magazine; "Reminiscences of General Lee," The Outlook pages 964-969; "The Last Years of Lee" delivered to the United Daughters of the Confederacy; "The Robert E. Lee Birthday Celebration;" "Lee Centennial at Washington and Lee," from The Southern Collegian; "On the Life and Character of Gen. Robert E. Lee," written by John W. Daniel for the Lexington Gazette; "Unveiling Lee's Statue," written by John W. Daniel for the Staunton Spectator; Article written for The Free-Lance Star by Capt. Robert Peniston entitled "The Last Tour;" Articled written by John Elrod for the Richmond Times-Dispatch entitled, "Lee as Educator Sought to Heal Wounds;" and an Article written by Captain James L.D. Monroe entitled "General Robert E. Lee Covers."
    The file includes excerpts from letters written by Agnes Lee to her friend Lizzie Fuller and Mrs. R.E. Lee concerning Robert E. Lee's death, as well as "General Lee's Special Letters," notes used by Captain Peniston during his talk to the Alumni College at Washington and Lee, July 2006. There are two chapters from two books: "College Days Under General Lee," chapter 6 of the book, Memories of Four-Score Years by Samuel Hall Chester; "The Lee-White Friendship," chapter 7 of Old Zeus: Life and Letters of James J. White.
    Finally, the file includes remarks on Robert E. Lee made at Kiwanis by Capt. Robert Peniston, an essay entitled "Lee at Appomattox," photocopies of two sketches by Robert E. Lee of soldiers in the Mexican Army sent home to his children, a copy of an endorsement of young Robert E. Lee from William B. Leary, his teacher in Alexandria, and a program and flier of the memorial observance of Lee given by the Liberty Hall Volunteers re-enactment group and Washington and Lee Alumni.
    Eight items added to file.
    Program, Robert E. Lee Week, August 22-26, 1932, The Greenbrier and Cottages, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia.
    "A Tribute to General Robert E. Lee," by Dr. Julian C. Brown (1856-1904).
    An Interview with General Robert E. Lee by John Leyburn. The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine. May to October 1885.
    The Hardy Heritage by Harold D. Garber, Moorefield (WV) Examiner, January 2010.
    Death of Gen. R. E. Lee, The Virginia Gazette, October 14, 1870.
    A Dream of Robert E. Lee Comes True, by Virgil C. Jones, The United States Publisher, September 1928.
    LEE, The Photographic History of the Civil War.
    "Cache," Autumn Song, by Ceane O'Hanlon-Lincoln.
    Lee, Robert E., General (Robert Edward); Washington and Lee University; Confederate States of America. Army. Liberty Hall Volunteers; Jackson, Thomas Jonathan (Stonewall); White, James J. (James Jones); Confederate States of America. Army; Peniston, Robert C.
  - Lee, Robert E. (Memorial Services) (Box 6, Folder 17)
    File includes various copies of programs for memorial services honoring Robert E. Lee as well as an article entitled "Decoration Day at the Graves of Lee and Jackson."
    Lee Chapel (Washington and Lee University); Washington and Lee University
  - Lee, Robert E. Col., Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.); Rockbridge County News (Box 6, Folder 18)
    File includes an obituary by the Lexington Gazette, articles in the Rockbridge County News and the Lexington Gazette concerning his death and funeral, one entitled "The Burial March of Dundee." In addition, the file includes a Ring-tum Phi article entitled, "May Remove Colonel Lee from Chapel."
    Lee, Robert E., III, Colonel (Robert Edward), 1869-1922
  - Lee, Robert E. Lee Jr. (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Lee, Robert E., Jr.
  - Lee, Robert Edward V (Box 6, Folder 20)
    File includes articles entitled "Children of the Blue and Gray," from People Magazine and "Robert E. Lee V Tries to Avoid Trading on His Honored Name" from The Atlanta Journal and Constitution.
    Lee, Robert E., V, 1963-
  - Lee Family, 1987-10-02 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    File includes articles entitled "On the Trail of Robert E. Lee's Daughters" and "Author Says Unmarried Women Neglected by Historians" from the Daily News Leader.
    Lee, Mary Custis; Lee, Annie Carter; Lee, Agnes; Lee, Mildred Childe
  - Leech, Holly (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Leech, Holly
  - Letcher, John Seymour (Box 6, Folder 23)
    File includes photocopies of two obituaries for Mr. Letcher, 1994.
    Letcher, John S. (John Seymour)
  - Lewis, Charles C. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    File includes an essay written by Charles C. Lewis entitled "A Tale of an Oar: A Hidden Message Revealed."
    Lewis, Charles C.
  - Lewis, Jim, 1875-12-17; Lexington Gazette. (Lexington, Va.) (Box 6, Folder 25)
    File includes obituaries of James Lewis, Stonewall Jackson's faithful body servant, Lexington Gazette.
    Lewis, James "Jim", -1875